Fear.
Glorious fear.
It's a natural emotion
present in all animals.
Now I'm curious.
Tell me, what do you think causes fear?
There is the kind of fear
born of animal instincts.
And the kind of fear born of a
rational mind that terrorizes humans.
Namely, when you encounter a
foe stronger than yourself?
And realize you have no way of
fighting back against the unknown!
Your helplessness begins to sink in.
and evokes inside of you a
terrible and paralyzing fear.
When you are faced with such fear,
you have a number of options
before you from which to choose.
You might struggle, resist,
flee, accept, or freeze.
But upon meeting Lord Dio, a
new unexpected reaction arises.
You feel joy!
How do you think most people
act once they feel joy and fear?
It's an interesting experience.
Our friend is currently on the plane
that Joestar and the others have boarded.
He'll greet them accordingly,
and they will find it
utterly impossible to
reach their final
destination in one piece.
A rhino beetle?
No, it's a stag beetle.
Hey, Avdol, is that a stand?
Are we already encountering
another stand user?
It's possible.
This could be a stem that takes
the shape of an insect. What the?
It hid in the shadow of the seats.
Damn.
It could be anywhere.
Jojo!
It's next to your head!
Look to your right!
Let's go.
I'll see you
next
time.
It's time to go!
Sit tight, I'll take care of it.
Be extremely careful.
I've heard that there is
a user of an insect stand
that likes to rip out the
tongues of his victims?
before they die.
Star Platinum!
It dodged you.
I, I can't believe it.
It's faster than Star Platinum, a
stand that has the speed and precision?
to grab a flying bullet.
Then there's no doubt about it.
That bug can only be a stand. Where is he?
Where is he hiding?
Where's the one who's controlling it?
We need to find him.
He's getting ready to attack.
No, damn it.
Jotaro!
Star Platinum stopped it with its
teeth just in the nick of time.
Just as I feared.
It's going after Jotaro's Stan's tongue.
It's him.
Represented by the
Tower Card of the Tarot.
Symbolizing Calamity and the interruption
of a journey, this stand is called...
Tower of Grey!
Tower of Grey is responsible
for countless mass murders,
which he made to look like
unfortunate accidents.
The plane crash last year in England that
caused over 300 deaths
was likely his work.
And how many more have
there been over the years?
I'd heard rumors, but to
think he's teamed up with Dio!
Hurrah!
It dodged that attack too?
Not just from the single hand, but it
also dodged a two-fisted barrage of blows!
It's so fast!
Even if you had ten guns to shoot
bullets from one centimeter away,
they would not be able to touch my stand!
Not that you could kill a
stand with a gun anyways,
you're all going to die with
the rest of these weaklings.
he has to be on this plane with us.
who is it who is the one
controlling the stand?
which one of the passengers is he?
if we can track him
down we can squash him.
he disappeared again.
heads up, it's over there now.
What's it planning to do?
No, it can't be.
Bingo, got their tongues.
Now for the best part!
Massacre!
Its definition?
To kill everyone!
No, it actually did it! Fine!
I'll burn that damn bug alive!
Go Magicians Red!
Avdol!
Just hold on a second!
It's so damn noisy on this flight.
What's with all the ruckus? Be careful!
Might as well go to the bathroom.
Why is this wet?
What's with all this slimy stuff?
Yes?
Blood!
This is blood!
Atum!
We have to defeat it before the
other passengers start to panic.
Easier said than done, though.
Mr. Avdol,
using an active stand
like your magician's red
inside an airborne plane
could make it explode,
killing all of us.
Jojo, if your power were to rip a hole
in the fuselage, it'd be a catastrophe.
This calls for a quiet and discreet stand.
My hierophant green is most
suited to defeating it.
Let me take care of the pest control.
I've heard all about you from Lord Dio.
Don't bother.
You think you have silence on your side.
But your stand cannot
keep up with my speed.
You sure about that?
Emerald Splash! Splash!
Emerald splash again!
You seem to think you can hit
me if you fire enough shots,
but you haven't hit me at all.
Not good.
It's dodging everything he throws at it.
Kacueing!
I'm just too fast for you.
You're way too slow to get a bingo.
And Kakyoin,
with my next attack, I'll stab your
Stan's tongue with this tower needle?
and rip it out.
Won't that be fun?
Emerald Splash!
Don't you get it?
Damn, impossible.
How can he win if his attacks
don't find their mark?
You'll go mad from the pain
once this rips its tongue out.
How exquisite!
Sad right.
If its tongue's ripped out,
I'll go mad from the pain?
My hierophant green
will go mad, all right.
What? Ow!
If it rips you apart, it'll go mad.
From pure joy.
His appendages had already
slipped beneath the seats.
I just needed enough time
to set up my little trap.
You didn't realize I was using my
emerald splash to keep you in one spot?
What the...?
So that geezer was the
user all along, huh?
Um, guess I should have expected as much.
A repulsive stand usually
has a repulsive user.
Well, that's strange.
It doesn't look like he had
Dio's flesh butt in his forehead.
Tower of Grey was always evil.
He killed Turris by the
hundreds and got paid for it.
He'd make it look like an accident
and got away with it every time.
I'm sure Tio was able to use him because
he was easily bought and blinded by greed
Something's wrong.
It could be my imagination,
but I get the feeling this plane
isn't flying straight anymore
It's crooked no doubt about it.
Eh, it can't be
Sorry, sir, you can't be up here.
The cockpit is up ahead, so
passengers may not enter.
I know that!
Sir, wait!
He's so handsome!
Move it, bitch!
What a shock!
Whoa there. Sorry, ladies.
His disrespectful behavior
towards you two is incorrigible.
But we have an emergency on our hands.
Please forgive him for me? Okay.
Damn it.
This is horrible.
We've been had their tongues
have been ripped out.
That rhino bastard.
He killed the pilots
before we knew he was here.
Hmm.
We're losing altitude fast.
The autopilot's been destroyed as well.
Damn it!
We're going to crash!
What?
My Stand at the Tower card would signify
horrible accidents and the end of journey.
I'll keep you from Lord Dio
if it's the last thing I do.
Even if you manage to survive the crash,
you're still 10,000 kilometers from Egypt.
Those who swore loyalty to Lord
Dio will pursue you relentlessly.
You don't stand a chance in hell.
There are stands in this world with powers
that defy the very limits of imagination.
Lord Dio's power is the one
that rules over all of them.
He is the master of stands, reigning
over the world like a god among mortals.
There's no way you'll reach them alive.
You bastards won't even see Egypt!
Your deaths will be swift and painful!
You're definitely professionals.
Good thing you didn't scream.
That annoys me all to freaking hell.
Now, I've got a request.
This heap's gonna hit water, and
this old man's gonna land her there.
Go put life jackets on the other passengers,
and make sure they're buckled up.
Yes, sir.
You've got this? Hmm.
I have some experience with prop
planes, but this... Prop planes?
But, Jotaro, this will make
three plane crashes for me.
Have you ever heard of someone
being in a plane crash three times?
Let alone surviving each one?
That settles it.
I'm never riding in a
plane with you again.
The plane landed 35 kilometers
off the coast of Hong Kong.
Jotaro and the others had no
choice but to head to the city.
South of Hong Kong near Lama Island.
Rescue efforts are now underway.
Hong Kong!
Hong Kong Island, Kowloon,
the New Territories.
With more than 235 individual
islands in the area,
its breathtaking nightscape is known the
world over as the Million Dollar View.
Yeah, no problem.
That'll be fine.
Please make sure the only ones
aboard are us and the crew.
Right.
There's been enough collateral
damage because of us.
By the way...
Hey, big guy!
You guys aren't from around here, are you?
Want some rice porridge?
Can't come to Hong Kong and I try
our rice porridge and dim sum?
We have some hot cola, too!
Rice porridge, not bad.
Did you know, Jojo, unlike in Japan, rice
porridge is a staple food in Hong Kong.
To some, it's quite a delicacy.
One bowl, the popular way with pork
and century egg, if you have it.
Coming right up!
In that case, I'll have...
Hey!
What?
You boys think we have time to eat?
We're going to my old favorite.
You can wait to stuff your faces there.
Hey, you dandy guy over there.
I know you'd be interested in
some Hong Kong hot cola. Hot cola?
That's blasphemy.
Everyone knows it's supposed to be cold.
Old man, who were you just calling?
Oh, that.
I'll explain when we
get to the restaurant.
Be patient.
We need to work out a plan that'll get us
to Egypt as safely and
quickly as possible.
More users are bound to come after
us, and that could cost lives.
Right. A plan.
I agree with you.
We can't allow any more innocent civilians
to be hurt because of our failure.
The quickest way would be
by plane, but that's out.
Indeed.
It's now become completely
impossible for us to fly to Egypt.
You see,
if we encounter a STAN user like
the last one on a commercial flight,
we'll cause a disaster.
One that will harm many people
and might kill many more.
With that in mind, we'll have to
get to Egypt by either land or sea.
I hear you, but if we fail
to find Dio within 50 days…
If we could have stayed on that plane,
we'd probably be in Cairo
and this would be over.
I'm well aware of that.
However, it's too soon to worry about it.
100 years ago, Jules Verne wrote
Around the World in 80 Days,
a story about a man who travels
40,000 kilometers in 11 weeks?
using nothing but trains and steamboats.
We may not have a plane,
but we still have 50 days.
We'll be able to travel the
10,000 kilometers to Egypt.
And as for the route we'll take,
I say, we go by sea.
We'll charter a suitably sized boat,
Go around the Malay Peninsula
and cross the Indian Ocean,
a silk road of the sea, as it were.
I believe that is best as well.
Crossing by land could be difficult,
and we'd have to cross the
Himalayas or the desert.
If we ran into trouble,
we'd lose a lot of time.
There are too many dangers.
I haven't been to any of those
places using either route before,
so I really don't know.
I'll leave it up to the two of you.
Same with me.
Then it's decided.
Now,
the greatest danger
that we'll face will be
the stand users that Dio sends against us.
We'll have to do our best to get
to Egypt without being spotted.
Don't be so jumpy.
This is just to let them
know we want more tea.
If you do this in Hong Kong, they'll
usually bring you more within a few seconds.
Also, any time the server
pours some tea into your cup,
tap the table.
It's a way of saying thank you.
Excuse me.
Sorry to be a bother.
I'm a tourist from France.
Could you help me out?
My Chinese is a bit rusty,
and I'm having a hard time with
the characters on the menu.
Could you help me decipher it?
You're annoying.
Go away.
Come now, Jotaro. It's fine.
Try to be nice to the man.
I've been to Hong Kong
many times over the years.
I can at least read the
characters on the menus.
Why don't you join us?
So, what do you want to order?
Dish with shrimp, duck,
shark fin, and mushrooms?
We'll have this, this, and this.
And might as well get some of these.
Oh, and this.
These look like dishes with
beef, fish, clams, and frog.
Indeed, this is quite
different from our order!
I knew this would happen, damn it.
Well, it makes no difference.
It's all on me, boys.
Besides, it doesn't matter what you order.
It's all delicious.
All right, everyone, dig in!
Oh,
this is you see that and you were
worried well they've certainly taken a lot
of time to prepare this it's almost
artistic take these carrots for example
cut into perfect little stars in
fact it reminds me of something
I remember now someone I know
has a mark a birthmark just
like this on the back of their
neck Know anyone like that?
Are you another enemy?
Hmm.
Mr.
Joestar, look out!
It's a stand!
Magician's Red, come forth!
What the hell?
You were right, another stand user.
Huh? Whoa.
He has such speed with his sword.
My stand is the chariot card,
and his name is Silver Chariot.
Mohamed Avdol, it seems that I
will be disposing of you first.
I've carved a burning
clock into that table.
Before that clock strikes
twelve, you will be a dead man.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick, oh-way-oh.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the fires are men by the Nile.
They got the money on a bet.
Called crocodiles.
Oh-eh-oh.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hookah. I say.
Oh-eh-oh.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
They spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink then
they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of folks.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian?
Care to become friends?
Tragedy gnaws away at your soul.
Work with me and your suffering
will soon be a thing of the past.
Your left hand wouldn't happen to
be a right hand of the bet club?
Challenging a fortune teller in a
battle of predictions is a bold move!